So now its important to choose the right record that will actually work together when you're trying to beat match.
The first thing to rule out if you want to do any extensive beat matching is to pick records that stay the same speed throughout the entire record.
A lot of older records, a lot of rock records, and especially a lot of, pretty much records that came out before the eighties.
A lot of them do not stay the same speed throughout the whole record and that will get you into horrible trouble because you match it and then it comes off.
And its just going to be really difficult to match it.
You're going to wonder what your problem.
Your problem is these records don't stay the same speed.
Also, you need to pick records that are even close enough in speed that they can be matched.
I was showing you with the pitch shifter that there's a finite range of how slow or how fast any particular record can get.
If we wanted to match these two records, I'll show you real quick.
Its not really going to be possible because this is just so much slower than this.
We've got this playing this speed, this is a lot slower.
You're never going to be able to get this record and this record to be the same speed because they're so far apart.